<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Football Club Studio</string>
    <string name="dummy_league_title">English Premier League</string>
    <string name="dummy_league_desc">the Premier League (often referred to as the English Premier League (EPL) outside England), is the top level of the English football league system. Contested by 20 clubs, it operates on a system of promotion and relegation with the English Football League (EFL).\r\n\r\nThe Premier League is a corporation in which the member clubs act as shareholders. Seasons run from August to May with each team playing 38 matches (playing each other home and away). Most games are played on Saturday and Sunday afternoons. The Premier League has featured 47 English and two Welsh clubs since its inception, making it a cross-border league.\r\n\r\nThe competition was formed as the FA Premier League on 20 February 1992 following the decision of clubs in the Football League First Division to break away from the Football League, founded in 1888, and take advantage of a lucrative television rights deal. The deal was worth £1 billion a year domestically as of 2013–14, with BSkyB and BT Group securing the domestic rights to broadcast 116 and 38 games respectively. The league generates €2.2 billion per year in domestic and </string>
    <string name="dummy_club_name">Arsenal</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detail_league">DetailLeagueActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_league_detail">LeagueDetailActivity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="search_event">Search Event</string>
    <string name="next_match">Next Match</string>
    <string name="last_match">Last Match</string>
    <string name="search_event_hint">Search match on &#032;</string>
    <string name="search_team_hint">Search team on &#032;</string>
    <string name="loading_search">Now loading to get data</string>
    <string name="round_tv">Round :</string>
    <string name="separator_score">:</string>
    <string name="goal_details">Goal Details</string>
    <string name="red_cards">Red Cards</string>
    <string name="yellow_cards">Yellow Cards</string>
    <string name="goalkeeper">Goalkeeper</string>
    <string name="defender">Defender</string>
    <string name="midfielder">Midfielder</string>
    <string name="forwarder">Forwarder</string>
    <string name="substitutes">Substitutes</string>
    <string name="favourite">favourite</string>
    <string name="formation">Formation</string>
    <string name="fav_removed">Match removed from favourite</string>
    <string name="fav_added">Added to favorite</string>
    <string name="loading_leagues">Now run to get league …</string>
    <string name="more_than_60">more than 60</string>
    <string name="fav_match">fav match</string>
    <string name="less_than_30">less than 30</string>
    <string name="just_10_item">just 10 item</string>
    <string name="classement">Classement</string>
    <string name="list_team">List Team</string>
    <string name="std_dump">
        The Emirates Stadium (known as Ashburton Grove prior to sponsorship) is a football stadium in Holloway, London, England, and the home of Arsenal Football Club. With a capacity of 60,272, the Emirates is the third-largest football stadium in England after Wembley and Old Trafford.In 1997, Arsenal explored the possibility of relocating to a new stadium, having been denied planning permission by Islington Council to expand its home ground of Highbury. After considering various options (including purchasing Wembley), the club bought an industrial and waste disposal estate in Ashburton Grove in 2000. A year later they won the councils approval to build a stadium on the site; manager Arsène Wenger described this as the "biggest decision in Arsenal's history" since the board appointed Herbert Chapman. Relocation began in 2002, but financial difficulties delayed work until February 2004. Emirates Airline was later announced as the main sponsor for the stadium. Work was completed in 2006 at a cost of £390 million
    </string>
    <string name="club_desc_dump">
        Arsenal Football Club is a professional football club based in Holloway, London which currently plays in the Premier League, the highest level of English football. One of the most successful clubs in English football, they have won 13 First Division and Premier League titles and a joint record 11 FA Cups.\r\n\r\nArsenals success has been particularly consistent: the club has accumulated the second most points in English top-flight football, hold the ongoing record for the longest uninterrupted period in the top flight, and would be placed first in an aggregated league of the entire 20th century. Arsenal is the second side to complete an English top-flight season unbeaten (in the 2003–04 season), playing almost twice as many matches as the previous invincibles Preston North End in the 1888–89 season.\r\n\r\nArsenal was founded in 1886 in Woolwich and in 1893 became the first club from the south of England to join the Football League. In 1913, they moved north across the city to Arsenal Stadium in Highbury. In the 1930s, they won five League Championship titles and two FA Cups. After a lean period in the post-war years they won the League and FA Cup Double, in the 1970–71 season, and in the 1990s and first decade of the 21st century, won two more Doubles and reached the 2006 UEFA Champions League Final. Since neighbouring Tottenham Hotspur, the two clubs have had a fierce rivalry, the North London derby.\r\n\r\nArsenal have one of the highest incomes and largest fanbases in the world. The club was named the fifth most valuable association football club in the world, valued at £1.3 billion in 2014.
    </string>
    <string name="established">Established:</string>
</resources>
